offerflip.com 2016-02-01

# Offerflip

OfferFlipcares about your privacy and takes it very seriously. Please read the following to learn more about our privacy policy. By visiting OfferFlip.com, you are accepting the practices outlined in this Privacy Policy.

## What does this Privacy Policy cover?

This Privacy Policy covers OfferFlip's treatment of personal information that OfferFlip gathers when you are on the OfferFlip website and when you use OfferFlip services.

This policy does not apply to the practices of third parties that OfferFlip does not own or control, or to individuals that OfferFlip does not employ or manage. 

## What personal information about users does OfferFlipcollect?

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with a friendly, customized, and efficient experience. We only collect personal information that is relevant to the purpose of our website. We do not process this information in a way that is incompatible with the purpose for which it has been collected or subsequently authorized by you. 

## Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We collect certain aggregate and non-personally identifiable information, when you visit this Site. This information does not relate to a single identifiable visitor. It tells us such things as how many users visited our Site and the pages accessed.

OfferFlip may use such information for its internal purposes, including, but not limited to, email and web design optimizations, new features, and editorial and feedback purposes. Information entered may be aggregated across all users in order to determine and target demographics for marketing and advertising purposes.

All user information stored by OfferFlip is considered confidential and will not be shared with outside parties. OfferFlipmay share aggregated results of preferences for all users for marketing and advertising purposes.

If you object to such use for any reason, you can either let us know by sending us feedback, or you can unsubscribe from the OfferFlip email service.

## What about cookies?

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our website are visited and by how many people. OfferFlip cookies do not collect personal information, and we do not combine information collected through cookies with other personal information to tell us who you are or what your screen name or email address is.

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our website (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

## Will OfferFlipshare any of the information it receives?

Information about our users is an integral part of our business. We neither rent nor sell your personal information to anyone. We share your personal information only as described below.

Protection of OfferFlip and others: We may release personal information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with that law; enforce or apply our conditions of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of OfferFlip, our employees, our users, or others.

With your consent: Except as set forth above, you will be notified when your personal information may be shared with third parties or used for a purpose incompatible with the purpose(s) for which it was originally collected, and you will be able to prevent the sharing of this information by opting out..

## Storage of User Information

OfferFlip stores any User Information in a database on secure computers. Our computers have security measures (such as a firewall) in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. But notwithstanding such measures, OfferFlip cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent the Company computers from being illegally accessed, and the data on them stolen or altered, and the Company assumes no responsibility for such actions. OfferFlip will store user information for 5 Years. You may request that your information be modified or deleted as detailed below.

## Age Appropriate Content

OfferFlipis not intended for use by children, especially those under age 13. No one under age 13 is allowed to use the site, provide any personal information or receive our email distributions. Minors between the ages of 13 and 17 must get the permission of their parent(s)or legal guardian(s) before viewing the website or receiving emails. All users must verify they're over the age of 18 on the OfferFlip site when viewing anycontent related to alcohol or tobacco.

## How do I Unsubscribe?

To unsubscribe, click on the unsubscribe link in any OfferFlip email. You will be taken to a confirmation page.  
Click on the confirm link and you will be unsubscribed. You can also unsubscribe by sending an email to support@OfferFlip.com

## Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in  
place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Although we take reasonable technological precautions to protect your data, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. 

## Social Media (Features) and Widgets: 

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it. 

## Modifications to Privacy Policy

OfferFlip reserves the right to change this policy from time to time, however, all changes will be posted to this Privacy Policy at the time such changes are made. The date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page so please check back. Please note that continued access of OfferFlipwill constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to the Privacy Policy.

If you have concerns or questions about any aspect of the OfferFlip's Privacy Policy, please e-mail us. We welcome your questions and feedback. Please send all emails to: support @OfferFlip.com. Our corporate mailing address is: 31312 Via Colinas, ste: 110, Westlake Village, CA 91362.

_Last modified: April 10th, 2012_

## Conditions of use

If you decide to visit OfferFlip website, your visit and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms & Conditions, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of California state law.

If you have any other questions about our privacy policy, shoot an email to  
support@OfferFlip.com

## Privacy Complaints

If you believe that we have not complied with this Privacy Policy, please contact our Home Office at:  
(805) 603-9912

Sincerely,

The OfferFlip Team

OfferFlip.com   
31312 Via Colinas, ste: 110  
Westlake Village, CA 91362.
